<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[thinking...]]></title><description><![CDATA[learning how to learn]]></description><link>https://musedivision.github.io/blog</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 07:12:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Zero to Deep learning]]></title><description><![CDATA[Quit job. Study 3 months. Become Deep learning researcher. ]]></description><link>https://musedivision.github.io/blog/posts/3months-to-deep-learning/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://musedivision.github.io/blog/posts/3months-to-deep-learning/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 22:40:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- ![daniel hertzberg](./daniel_hertzberg_artificial_intelligence_with_human_feelings.jpg) --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am embarking on an ambitious learning project for the next 3 months:&lt;br&gt;
Learning deep learning and the mathematics behind it by studying only online resources such as fastai, MIT opencourseware and YouTube.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--![placeholder photo](./1.jpg)--&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Why deep learning?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deep learning is cool! Its like particle physics in the early 20th Century crossed with the advent of Personal computers in the 70s!
New and exciting frontiers are open to discover the fundamental building blocks of intelligence and the barrier to entry is just a computer with access to the internet. It feels like a unique moment in human history and I am very excited by it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Starting with random weights&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My background isn’t in machine learning or mathematics.  I study Psychology for 5 years at University but only ever took a couple of papers in statistics. I never thought that mathematics would be something I would be interested in.
I have no idea about linear algebra or calculus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a Javascript developer by trade.
Three years ago I self studied coding using Freecodecamp (ref) for 8months. I was lucky to get a chance by the New Zealand Forsite(link) gave me a chance as an intern. Fast forward to now. I have been writing Javascript professionally for 2 years and I still feel like an imposter some days.  So why not feel like an imposter doing deep learning?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;So naïve&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clearly you are misguided if I believe that you can just learn in 3 months what takes a PhD student years! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok I admit the goal is a little preposterous.&lt;br&gt;
I may have gotten the wrong idea from Jeremy Howard and Rachel Thomas (ref). I found their deep learning for coders course in 2017 &lt;a href=&quot;#ref_6&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;6&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and was given the idea that it was possible to learn math even if you were not good at it before AND that you can make meaningful contributions to deep learning research if you take a practical top down approach to learning it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that blissful ignorance about the difficulty we can happily skip into plan ⬇️&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;🧳 The Plan&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope to build a strong foundational knowledge in the practical methods for building deep learning systems and the mathematics involved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Machine Learning and Deep learning&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;Course/Book&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;FTE&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Cost&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;Fastai&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;- Practical Deep Learning for Coders Part 1 (2019)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;- Deep Learning Part 2 (2019) (not released yet)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1.5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;Deeplearning.ai&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;- Deep learning specialization&lt;a href=&quot;#ref_1&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;em&gt;$45&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;Jeremy Khun&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;- Programmers Introduction to Mathematics Book &lt;a href=&quot;#ref_2&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;MIT&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;- XXXX Single Variable Calculus&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;- 18.02 Multivariable Calculus&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;- 18.06 Linear Algebra&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.7&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;- 18.065 Matrix Methods in Data analysis, signal processing and machine learning&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.7&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;3Blue1Brown&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;- Essence of Linear Algebra &amp;#x26; Calculus&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;Khan Academy&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;- Linear Algebra &amp;#x26; Calculus&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;Udemy&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;- Swift - iOS app development &lt;a href=&quot;#ref_3&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;- Python for data science and machine learning &lt;a href=&quot;#ref_4&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;0.3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;$11&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;Resources&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;GPU server instance  - AWS p2 instance &amp;#x3C;200 hours&lt;a href=&quot;#ref_5&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;~$300&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Total&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;7.4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;~$367&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Focus and FTE Points:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beside each course you’ll see a number which is my arbitrary Full Time Effort metric.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;1 point&lt;/strong&gt; being the full focus of a university paper for &lt;strong&gt;1 semester&lt;/strong&gt; ( ~ 12 weeks ).
Of course it is arbitrary, but my idea behind this is to quantify, like in Scrum (ref), the complexity of AND effort I will spend on each course. Basically the less effort the more content I will skip from the course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plan comes out to about 7.5 points. By the above definition this is nearly twice the amount of work I can fit into 12 weeks! Lets see what happens…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;📜 Do you get a certificate?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I get asked this question by almost every person I tell my plan to.
I understand that university degrees and other certificates are important proofs of your proficiency in a subject.
I wont get a cerificate.
For me, someone who found their University Certificates (BSc in Psychology, PostGrad Diploma in Psychology) not so useful when looking for jobs. For many entry level positions people do not simply trust your proficiency in a subject because you have degree.
When I learnt to code my certificate was my projects. People had not heard of FreeCodeCamp so their certificates were not worth much. The projects I built during the FreeCodeCamp curriculum were however undeniable proof. Github was the proof. You can hire me to write &lt;em&gt;javascirpt to build websites&lt;/em&gt;, because here, I have built websites using javascript.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rightly or wrongly I will follow this philosophy for deep learning.
Models in production with code on Github, implementing papers in code and technical writing will be my certificate of proficiency for deep learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Why not do a Masters&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good question. I would have the chance to basically do what I am doing but in a more supported environment with capable peers to collaborate with and learn from etc. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost&lt;/strong&gt;: a Masters in NZ would cost at least 10k plus the opportunity cost of one years income.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Low Risk&lt;/strong&gt;:  3 months of studying online wont cost me very much &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And if its not for me in the end, well I can get a job writing Javascript again ( I love being a developer, so it’s a great second best ) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do believe also, as between Computer science and Software development, that the practical skills required to produce good results are not necessarily found in a Masters or Doctorate Program. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Three years ago I quit my job to study coding online ( 🙌 Freecodecamp  ). It took 8months full time learning before this great startup Forsite(link) gave me a chance as an intern. Once there I was incredibly lucky to have a mentor who believed in Pair programming (two people on the same computer, solving the same problem sharing the mouse and keyboard) . For 2 years I worked with developers who were better than me everyday; all day. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My track into the field of programming, which is usually presumed you should have a Computer science degree, has given me the idea you can break into such fields without a formal academic degree.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The unknown:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;blockquote&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;There is what you know you know. &lt;br/&gt; 
		What you know you dont know &lt;br/&gt; 
		And what you dont know what you dont know&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;footer&gt;
			&lt;cite&gt;— Maybe Donald Rumsfield?&lt;/cite&gt;
		&lt;/footer&gt;
	&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like the above quote because I feel it summarises way you are encouraged to think about complexity in the software development ideology of scrum (ref).&lt;br&gt;
You have to be honest about the unknown complexity of the thing you are doing. There are things that you will learn about the problem you are solving along the way. By definintion these things will be &lt;strong&gt;unknown unknowns&lt;/strong&gt;. That is, you cant really prepare for them. You have to go in knowing that your understanding will change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For me, this idea holds for the learning process as well. Your understanding of what more you need to learn will expand and change as you learn more and understand your problems better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back to the current problem. I have self studied to break into a completely new field before. So at least the &lt;em&gt;process&lt;/em&gt; of embarking on a new endeavour like this is not completely new to me.&lt;br&gt;
But I have to be honest. I am not sure if I will be good or enjoy mathematics or deep learning.
I also don’t really know about the state of deep learning research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I am happy to find these things out, and I am happy to be wrong. Well if not happy I can come to accept it… &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the very least at the end of 3 months, I will have a pretty good idea of what I don’t know. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;🧠 Anki and Michael Neilson:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Part of this project will be my own meta learning project. Meta learning being a fancy way to say learning about learning. My own learning process that it ( not ML )
I was super inspired by an great post by Michael Neilson on Augmenting cognition (ref long but excellent read).
The post puts forward a some ideas and practical observations from using the personal memory system Anki.
The main thesis about learning goes something like this: Thinking about complex subjects is built upon many small bit of knowledge similar to how a chess grandmaster see a whole board at glance and understands it as collection of moves and strategies. Whereas a novice is overwhelmed and cannot fathom the whole 40 pieces at once! The grandmaster can break down the board into chunks of strategy which can be used a &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Micheal posits that a primary drag on cognition is that fact that we cannot reliably remember facts or theories are learning. That is that in general people do not retain most of what they study. The results of my university career attest to this. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anki is spaced repetition based flash card app. You write cards like below. When you answer them you rate how hard it was. With this information, the anki app will then remind you to review the card at an interval.
The whole idea is to hack the forgetting curve (ref). If you retreive the information at the correct time, you can strengthen the memory of the information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;blockquote&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;Cultivate a taste in what to Ankify&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;footer&gt;
			&lt;cite&gt;— Michael Nielsen&lt;/cite&gt;
		&lt;/footer&gt;
	&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My biggest takeaway from the article is the advice:
“Cultivate a taste in what to Ankify” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That is, the process of making your flash cards is the most important. A question can be too hard, too simple, unconnected to your other knowledge. You may have not understood the concept and reminding yourself to think about it will not magically make you understand it. I experienced all of these. It feels like you just have to do the time to understand when to add some thing and what kind of card is good to add.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be spending so much time learning that the idea of radically improving my retention of the knowledge excites me so much! I intend to write more about my experience with these techniques as I find out what works for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;( Michael has written a more recent article about the strategy for using anki to extridite the process of deeply understanding mathematical theory (ref) )&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Why I wrote this post?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I was a little terrified to write this blog post. In my mind I had a fewdifferent reasons to do it.
( A public and social commitment to my goal; Encourage others like me;  Share some insights that might be useful to others )&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mostly I have to blame Rachel Thomas and Jeremy Howard:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;blockquote&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;You have a unique perspective that is valuable for someone who is just behind you in the learning process. You understand what its like to be where they are,  better than someone further on&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;footer&gt;
			&lt;cite&gt;— Rachel Thomas &amp; Jeremy Howard&lt;/cite&gt;
		&lt;/footer&gt;
	&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be writing more, with that simple but powerful idea in mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;ref_1&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;I intend to take the deeplearning.ai course as supplement to fastai practical deep learning courses&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a id=&quot;ref_2&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;This book got me excited about the ideas and magic of mathematical proofs and the beauty behind it. It has helped to change my view of mathematics. I think of it like a foundational perspective on the subject, rather than a rigorous course to teach me many subjects.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a id=&quot;ref_3&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;Swift for Tensorflow seems important (ref)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a id=&quot;ref_4&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;To fill out some my practical knowledge of the python datascience ecosystem matplotlib, numpy etc.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a id=&quot;ref_5&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;Unknown how much this will cost as you can also use Google Colab with a GPU/TPU for free!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a id=&quot;ref_6&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;6&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;When I found the course I was actually searching for resources to learn about AWS and the first course included alot fiddily bits about setting up a GPU on AWS. Which I loved&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A Brief History of Typography]]></title><description><![CDATA[Morbi in sem quis dui placerat ornare. Pellentesque odio nisi, euismod in, pharetra a, ultricies in, diam. Sed arcu. Cras consequat.]]></description><link>https://musedivision.github.io/blog/posts/a-brief-history-of-typography/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://musedivision.github.io/blog/posts/a-brief-history-of-typography/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 22:40:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique&lt;/strong&gt; senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. &lt;em&gt;Aenean ultricies mi vitae est.&lt;/em&gt; Mauris placerat eleifend leo. Quisque sit amet est et sapien ullamcorper pharetra. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vestibulum erat wisi, condimentum sed, commodo vitae, ornare sit amet, wisi. Aenean fermentum, elit eget tincidunt condimentum, eros ipsum rutrum orci, sagittis tempus lacus enim ac dui.  &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Donec non enim&lt;/a&gt; in turpis pulvinar facilisis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-link&quot;
    href=&quot;/static/07d3a9ebe902d793eab5fe701b12a6e2/98235/1.jpg&quot;
    style=&quot;display: block&quot;
    target=&quot;_blank&quot;
    rel=&quot;noopener&quot;
  &gt;
  
  &lt;span
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-wrapper&quot;
    style=&quot;position: relative; display: block;  max-width: 960px; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&quot;
  &gt;
    &lt;span
      class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-background-image&quot;
      style=&quot;padding-bottom: 66.66666666666666%; position: relative; bottom: 0; left: 0; background-image: url(&apos;data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wBDABALDA4MChAODQ4SERATGCgaGBYWGDEjJR0oOjM9PDkzODdASFxOQERXRTc4UG1RV19iZ2hnPk1xeXBkeFxlZ2P/2wBDARESEhgVGC8aGi9jQjhCY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2P/wgARCAANABQDASIAAhEBAxEB/8QAFgABAQEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAwAE/8QAFQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAQL/2gAMAwEAAhADEAAAAVhO4azw/wD/xAAcEAABAwUAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABAAIhAxESMkH/2gAIAQEAAQUCBQkPxvKp6d//xAAUEQEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAQ/9oACAEDAQE/AT//xAAUEQEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAQ/9oACAECAQE/AT//xAAZEAACAwEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAARAhYXH/2gAIAQEABj8CmhaPp//EAB0QAQADAAEFAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEAESExQVFhcYH/2gAIAQEAAT8htrv1hy4LT3KNpfmLq1U1Oc66X7GnMxE//9oADAMBAAIAAwAAABBzD//EABYRAQEBAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEQIf/aAAgBAwEBPxAMn//EABYRAAMAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABIf/aAAgBAgEBPxBulP/EAB0QAQACAgIDAAAAAAAAAAAAAAERIQAxQWFRcbH/2gAIAQEAAT8QGINbBxwmBCYqnbfWOKqF2cQq2Gpdd/MAikmwMyMIXmCXn3n/2Q==&apos;); background-size: cover; display: block;&quot;
    &gt;
      &lt;img
        class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-image&quot;
        style=&quot;width: 100%; height: 100%; margin: 0; vertical-align: middle; position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; box-shadow: inset 0px 0px 0px 400px white;&quot;
        alt=&quot;Nulla faucibus vestibulum eros in tempus. Vestibulum tempor imperdiet velit nec dapibus&quot;
        title=&quot;&quot;
        src=&quot;/static/07d3a9ebe902d793eab5fe701b12a6e2/b3ee8/1.jpg&quot;
        srcset=&quot;/static/07d3a9ebe902d793eab5fe701b12a6e2/3bc27/1.jpg 240w,
/static/07d3a9ebe902d793eab5fe701b12a6e2/98431/1.jpg 480w,
/static/07d3a9ebe902d793eab5fe701b12a6e2/b3ee8/1.jpg 960w,
/static/07d3a9ebe902d793eab5fe701b12a6e2/b97fe/1.jpg 1440w,
/static/07d3a9ebe902d793eab5fe701b12a6e2/98235/1.jpg 1800w&quot;
        sizes=&quot;(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px&quot;
      /&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
  
  &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Header Level 2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetuer adipiscing elit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aliquam tincidunt mauris eu risus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donec non enim in turpis pulvinar facilisis. Ut felis. Praesent dapibus, neque id cursus faucibus, tortor neque egestas augue, eu vulputate magna eros eu erat. Aliquam erat volutpat. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;blockquote&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Vivamus magna. Cras in mi at felis aliquet congue. Ut a est eget ligula molestie gravida. Curabitur massa. Donec eleifend, libero at sagittis mollis, tellus est malesuada tellus, at luctus turpis elit sit amet quam. Vivamus pretium ornare est.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;footer&gt;
			&lt;cite&gt;— Aliquam tincidunt mauris eu risus.&lt;/cite&gt;
		&lt;/footer&gt;
	&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Header Level 3&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetuer adipiscing elit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aliquam tincidunt mauris eu risus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo. Quisque sit amet est et sapien ullamcorper pharetra.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;css&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;language-css&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-css&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token selector&quot;&gt;#header h1 a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;token property&quot;&gt;display&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; block&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;token property&quot;&gt;width&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; 300px&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;token property&quot;&gt;height&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; 80px&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vestibulum erat wisi, condimentum sed, commodo vitae, ornare sit amet, wisi. Aenean fermentum, elit eget tincidunt condimentum, eros ipsum rutrum orci, sagittis tempus lacus enim ac dui. Donec non enim in turpis pulvinar facilisis. Ut felis. Praesent dapibus, neque id cursus faucibus, tortor neque egestas augue, eu vulputate magna eros eu erat. Aliquam erat volutpat. Nam dui mi, tincidunt quis, accumsan porttitor, facilisis luctus, metus.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>